ILR School Dean's Office Course Descriptions /4325
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Dean's Office Course Descriptions
1945-1958
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations
ILR School Dean's Office
/4325
0.5 cubic feet
0.5 linear ft.
Records.
Descriptions of ILR courses offered, along with the class schedules.
9443915
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, May 10, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, May 10, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
9443915
- no.2 Curriculum: 4-year Course, 1945-1946 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Course Descriptions, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Scope and Contents
  Fall 1946
- Revised Schedule and Room Assignments, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  September 1947
- Course Descriptions, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Course Descriptions, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Elective Courses, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Course Descriptions, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Course Descriptions, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Course Descriptions, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Course Descriptions, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Course Descriptions, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Course Schedules, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Course Descriptions, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Course Schedule, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  Spring 1955
- Course Descriptions, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Course Schedules, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Course Descriptions, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Course Schedules, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Course Descriptions, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  Spring 1958
- Course Schedule, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 20)